#### Contact

christinapelletier@gmail.co

www.linkedin.com/in/ christinajoypelletier (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Blogging Personal Training Fitness Training

#### Languages

Spanish (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

# Christina Joy Pelletier, RN, BSN

PreOp and PACU RN at Tsehootsooi Medical Center Sacramento, California Area

# Summary

Motivated and driven Registered Nurse with over 4 years of healthcare experience. Thrives as a Registered Nurse in a challenging team care environment. Exemplary teaching skills with compassionate family centered care approach. Versed in critical thinking and holistic patient approach, physical, mental, emotional, and spiritual. Application of through assessments, planning, implementations, and evaluations.

# Experience

Tsehootsooi Medical Center PreOp and PACU RN March 2020 - Present (5 months) Fort Defiance, AZ

PreOp and PACU Registered Nurse

# Dignity Health Travel Float Pool Medical Surgical Telemetry RN October 2019 - Present (10 months)

Sacramento, California Area

Float pool registered nurse to Medical Surgical Telemetry departments to five local Dignity Health Hospitals.

#### Kaiser Permanente Travel Medical Surgical Telemetry RN December 2019 - March 2020 (4 months) Modesto, California

Kaweah Delta Health Care District Travel Medical Surgical Registered Nurse April 2019 - September 2019 (6 months) California Maxim Healthcare Services
Registered Nurse
April 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 4 months)
Sacramento, California Area

Closely assess, monitor, and observe changes in patient status, providing immediate care to patients with diabetes, epilepsy, asthma, allergies, heart conditions, and other life-threatening conditions. Administer life-saving medications in a timely and accurate manner. Medication management and reconciliation. Maintain professional and respectful rapport with personnel and nursing staff to promote positive patient environment. Communicate with clarity to patients and family, building trust during critical assessments and interventions.

Sanford Health Medical Specialty Unit Registered Nurse July 2018 - April 2019 (10 months) Fargo, North Dakota Area

Medical Specialty Unit with a comprehensive mix of complex medical patients, multi-disease process including pneumonia, palliative, renal disease, diabetes, dialysis, respiratory distress, cellulitis, encephalopathy, COPD, CHF, seizure, alcohol withdrawal, and psych patients. Admissions and discharges daily.

Coordinating with patient needs, family needs, doctors, pharmacists, telemetry, case workers, social workers, physical therapy, occupational therapy, dietary, interventional radiology, CNA's, unit registered nurses, ICU nurses, transport, charge nurse, unit manager, and unit supervisor.

Overseeing multiple CNA's on the unit with patient care needs and delegation. Caring and compassionate approach to meet the wholistic physical, spiritual, emotional, and mental needs of 4-6 unique patients in 12 hour shifts.

California State University, Sacramento RN, BSN
January 2016 - December 2017 (2 years)
Sacramento, California Area

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, GPA 3.85 California State University of Sacramento, Magna Cum Laude December 2017 Excellent work ethic in Nursing Clinical Rotations: Medical Surgical (Med-Surg), Trauma, Telemetry, Emergency Room (ER), Intensive Care Unit (ICU), Pediatrics, PICU, Labor and Delivery, Mother Baby, and Psychiatric Nursing.

Home Care Assistance Elderly Caregier February 2015 - January 2017 (2 years) Sacramento, California Area

Effectively assisted clients with activities of daily living to increase client and family outcomes. Completed all client documentation entries and updates improving accuracy of client needs, progress and outcomes. Duties included: Supervisor change in status communication, Overnight, Hospice, Activities of Daily Living, Medication Reminders, Incontinence care, Transfers, Meal Preparation, and Hygiene.

### Education

California State University-Sacramento
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016 - 2017)